Guide to the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace pamphlet and microfilm collection, 1817-1950 MS2110
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Unbound pamphlets, 1817-1950; MS2110 Series 2; 47 Linear feet
  - "House of Commons and German Rearmament", 1934 ca. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-19, Author: Baldwin, Stanley and Churchill, Winston; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 19
  - "Military Science of Professor Banse", 1934 ca. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-20, Author: Banse, Ewald; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 10
  - "Crucifying the Savior of France", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-21, Author: Barnes, Harry Elmer
  - "The German Struggle: Tribulation and Promise", 1939 ca. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-22, Author: Barth, Karl
  - "A Few Kind Words for Uncle Sam", 1948 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-23, Author: Baruch, Bernard M.
  - "Industrial Property in Europe", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-24, Author: Basch, Antonin
  - "Half of Humanity", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-25, Author: Bates, M. Searle
  - "Four Years of War", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-26, Author: Beaton, Grace M.
  - "When Germany is Defeated - ?", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-27, Author: Bedford, Hastings William, Sackville Russel
  - "U.S. Naval Detachment in Turkish Waters", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-28, Author: Beer, Henry P.
  - "25 Theses of the German Religion", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-29, Author: Bergmann, Karl Ernst; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 39
  - "Statistical Truth", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-30, Author: Bieligk, F. K.
  - "Yugoslavia and Her Struggle", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-31, Author: Bloom, Sol
  - "Will America be Dragged Into the Coming World War?", 1935 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-32, Author: Bone, T. Homer
  - "The Future of Germany", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-33, Author: Brailsford, H. N.
  - "Making Germany Pay?", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-34, Author: Brailsford, H. N.
  - "The Swarthmore College Peace Collection - A Memorial to Jane Addams", 1947 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-35, Author: Brinton, Ellen Star
  - "Address by the Most Hon. Marquess of Lothain at Columbia University Commencement", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-39, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "Address by the British Ambassador to the United States", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-40, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "The Allies and Finland" (excerpts from speeches), 1940 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-41, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "India and the War", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-42, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "Letters from Home", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-43, Author: British Library of Information
  - "Our Lives, Our Fortunes, and Our Sacred Honour", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-44, Author: British Library of Information
  - "Speech Broadcast by H.M. King George VI, May 24, 1940" (Box 10, Folder 42)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-45, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "Speech Broadcast by Viscount Halifax; July 22, 1940" (Box 10, Folder 43)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-46, Author: British Library of Information, The
  - "The Strategy of the Atlantic", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-47, Author: Brodie, Bernard, Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 2
  - "North Atlantic Relations - an Annotated Bibliography", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-48, Author: Brodie, Fawn M.; Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 10
  - "The Future of the Anglo-Soviet-American Coalition", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-49, Author: Browder, Earl
  - "The Immortal Peace Crusade", 1946 ca. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-50, Author: Brown, Kathryn
  - "South American Settlement for Refugees", 1939 ca. (Box 10, Folder 48)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-51, Author: Brown, H. Runham
  - "Vatican Information Service Contacts Friends and Relatives", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-52, Author: Butcher, Harold
  - "The Wartime Machinery of Canadian External Relations", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-53, Author: Carter, G.
  - "Speeches on Germany", 1933 ca. (Box 10, Folder 51)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-54, Author: Chamberlain, Austin; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 7
  - "Who's Who in a World at War", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-55, Author: Chandler, Tertius
  - "Address Given December 2, 1941" (Box 10, Folder 53)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-56, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Address Broadcast February 15, 1942" (Box 10, Folder 54)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-57, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Crimea Conference; Report of the Speech by the Prime Minister, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-58, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "On the Taking of the French Fleet", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-59, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech Broadcast July 14, 1940" (Box 10, Folder 57)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-60, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech Delivered in the House of Commons June 18, 1940" (Box 10, Folder 58)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-61, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech in the House of Commons; November 12, 1941" (Box 10, Folder 59)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-62, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech to the House of Commons; December 11th 1941" (Box 10, Folder 60)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-63, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech on the Far East War, December 8th, 1941", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-64, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Speech on the New War Delivered June 22, 1941" (Box 10, Folder 62)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-65, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Statement to the House of Commons; July 29, 1941" (Box 10, Folder 63)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-66, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "Statement to the House of Commons; September 30, 1941" (Box 10, Folder 64)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-67, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "To the People of France", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-68, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "To the Polish People", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-69, Author: Churchill, Winston
  - "When the Fighting Stops", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-70, Author: Cole, G. D. H.
  - "Japan and Some Aspects of the Japanese Situation", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-71, Author: Commercial and Financial Chronicle, The
  - "Memorandum on the Chatham House Committee on Reconstruction", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-72, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations
  - "Memorandum on Important Changes in the Labor Situation and Social Conditions in Great Britain Since Outbreak of War", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-73, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations
  - "Note as to Some Post-War Economic Problems", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-74, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations
  - "Note On Post-War Shipping Problems", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-75, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations
  - "Notes on German Military Potential and The Peace Settlement", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-76, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations
  - "The Future of Germany, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-77, Author: Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 13
  - "War Aims and Post War Plans, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-79, Author: Corbett, Percy E.; Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 1
  - "German Foreign Policy Before the War", 1934 ca. (Box 10, Folder 76)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-80, Author: Crowe, Eyre; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 16
  - "The Paramount Question" (Air Power), 1944 ca. (Box 10, Folder 77)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-81, Author: Davies, David
  - "The Problem of Neutrality", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-82, Author: Den, C.G.
  - "Peace or War the People against War Makers", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-83, Author: Dennis, Eugene
  - "International Declarations on War Policy", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-84, Author: Department of External Affairs, Wellington
  - "Japan's Expansion - What it Means to the United States", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-85, Author: Douglas, Henry H.
  - "Germany, Great Britain and the League of Nations", 1935 ca. (Box 10, Folder 82)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-86, Author: Eden, Anthony; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 24
  - "Principles of British Foreign Policy", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 83)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-87, Author: Eden, Anthony; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 33
  - "Communism in Germany", 1933 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-88, Author: Ehrt, Adolf
  - "Europe's Danger: Europe's Hope", 1933 ca. (Box 10, Folder 85)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-89, Author: Einstein, Albert; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 4
  - "Eisenhower on War and Peace", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-90, Author: Eisenhower, Dwight David
  - "Louvain During the War", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-91, Author: Essen, Leon Vander
  - "Were We Unfair to Germany Last Time?", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-92, Author: Flournoy, F.R.
  - "Peace", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-93, Author: Floyd, Mcknight
  - "Final Secret of Pearl Harbor", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-94, Author: Flynn, John T.
  - "Keep the Embargo on Arms", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-95, Author: Follette, Robert M. La, Jr.
  - "Food Relief for Occupied Europe", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-96, Author: Foot, Dingle M.
  - "Economic Measures Essential for Winning the Peace", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-97, Author: Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Our Foreign Trade In Relation to the War", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-98, Author: Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Summary of Various Current Proposals for Post War International Economic Action", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-99, Author: Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Treatment of United Stated Property in Enemy Countries", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-100, Author: Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Prepare to Occupy", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-101, Author: Fortune magazine
  - "What Can the Colleges do for Peace?", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-102, Author: Gaines, Francis P.
  - "Confessions: The Religious Conflict in Germany", 1934 ca. (Box 10, Folder 99)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-103, Author: Garvie, A. E.; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 20
  - "Hitler and Arms", 1937 ca. (Box 10, Folder 101)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-104, Author: Garvin, James L.; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 1
  - "Germany Re-Arming: A Study of the Actual Situation in Germany", 1933 ca. (Box 10, Folder 102)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-105, Author: "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 5
  - "The Price of Victory Inside Greece", 1941-1944 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-106, Author: Greek Office of Information, Authority of the
  - "Labour Problems in Relation to Defense", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-107, Author: Greenwood, Arthur
  - "Russia Fights Famine; A Russian War Relief Report", 1944 ca. (Box 10, Folder 105)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-108, Author: Gruliow, Leo and Lederer, Sidoniek.
  - "The Balance of Power, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-109, Author: Gulick, Edward Vose; The Pacifist Research Bureau, No.2
  - "Round Table Terms or Unconditional Surrender for Japan?", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-110, Author: Gulick, Leeds Hutchinson, Paul and Lattimore, Owen
  - "American-Japanese Problem", 1914 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-111, Author: Gulick, Sidney L.
  - "Challenge to Youth", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-112, Author: Halifax, Edward
  - "Text of Address Numan Menemchioglu Foreign Minister of Turkey to the Grand National Assembly, April 20, 1944" (Box 10, Folder 110)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-113, Author: Hariclye, Vekaleti
  - "Common Wealth in Arms", 1940 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-114, Author: Harlow, Vincent
  - "Free Man or State Slave", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-115, Author: Hart, B.H. Liddell
  - "There Must be No Germany after This War", 1942 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-116, Author: Heartman, Charles Frederick
  - "Japan's Dual Rulership Political, Religious, Zodiacal", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-117, Author: Heline, Theodore
  - "Twelve Dates with Destiny" [Poland and WWII], 1944 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-118, Author: Hensell, Hester E.
  - "A Handbook for the Information of Relatives", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-119, Author: His Majesty's Stationery Office
  - "Germany's Foreign Policy", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 117)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-120, Author: Hitler, Adolf; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 38
  - "Hitler the Man", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 118)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-121, Author: Hitler, Adolf; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 34
  - "Racial Conception of the World", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 119)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-122, Author: Hitler, Adolf; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 37
  - "Hitler's Thirteen Points", 1935 ca. (Box 10, Folder 120)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-123, Author: Hitler, Adolf; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 29
  - "Hitler - Germany and Europe", 1937 ca. (Box 10, Folder 121)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-124, Author: "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 2
  - "America's World Purpose" (Life Magazine Article), 1944 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-125, Author: Hocking, William Ernest
  - "The State of the Nation", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-126, Author: Hocking, William et. al
  - "International Law or International Chaos", 1934 ca. (Box 10, Folder 124)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-127, Author: Howard, E. W., "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 18
  - "Prevention of War by Collective Action", 1933 ca. (Box 10, Folder 125)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-128, Author: Howard, E. W.; "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 8
  - "The Menace of Native Fascism in America after World War II", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-129, Author: Howell, Charles Garfield
  - "Letter to Hon. Henry Morgenthau Concerning a Report on the Acts of German Cruelty and Wanton Destruction Committed in Naples", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-130, Author: Hume, Edgar Erskine
  - "Japan Need not Fear the United States", 1932 ca. (Box 10, Folder 128)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-131, Author: Ikezaki, Chuko
  - "Facts about India's War Effort", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-132, Author: India Information Services, Government of
  - "India At War", 1945 ca. (Box 10, Folder 130)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-133, Author: India Information Services, Government of
  - "India's Five Years of War", 1945 ca. (Box 10, Folder 131)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-134, Author: India Information Service, Government of
  - "India Shares Victory in the West", 1940 ca. (Box 10, Folder 132)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-135, Author: India Information Service, Government of
  - "There is Another Way", 1946 ca. (Box 10, Folder 133)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-136, Author: International Arbitration League, The
  - "The Permanent Basis of Japanese Foreign Policy", 1933 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-137, Author: Ishii, Viscount Kikujiro
  - "The Franco-British Financial Agreement of December 1939", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-138, Author: Istel, Andre; Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 9
  - "A Peace to End Wars?", 1947 ca. (Box 10, Folder 136)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-139, Author: Jacob, Betty Muther
  - "Nisei in Uniform", 1944 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-140, Author: Japanese American Citizens League
  - "Our Far Eastern Record: The War Years", 1946 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-141, Author: Jenkins, Shirley
  - "Hitler's Death Warrant!", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-142, Author: Johnson, Hewlett
  - "Atlantic Union the Way to Peace; Reply to State Department", 1950 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-143, Author: Kefauver, Hon. Estes
  - "Germany Puts the Clock Forward", 1933 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-144, Author: Keller, Hans
  - "The New Constitution of Albania: A Model Constitution for European Vassal States", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-145, Author: Kempner, Robert M. W.
  - Over"How to Save the Starving Children of Europe Without sizedAiding the Enemy", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-146, Author: Kershner, E. Howard
  - "The Complete Address", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-147, Author: Knox, Franklin
  - "Nazi Germany's Foreign Policy", 1945 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-148, Author: Krzesinski, Andrew J.
  - "Creed of the Nordic Race", 1936 ca. (Box 10, Folder 146)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-149, Author: Kusserow, Wilhelm, "Friends of Europe" Pub. no. 31
  - "The Economic Revolution", 1941 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-150, Author: Laski, Harold J.
  - "London (England), Washington, Moscow, Partners in Peace?", 1943 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-151, Author: Laski, Harold J.
  - "Public Opinion and British - American Unity", 1941 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-152, Author: Lasswell, Harold D.; Conference on North Atlantic Relations - Document 4
  - "Strategic Bases", 1944 ca. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-153, Author: League of Nations Association (typescript)
  - "The Atlantic Charter", 1942 (Box 11, Folder 3 item 1)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-154, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "Atlantic Charter and the League", 1942 (Box 11, Folder 3 item 2)
  - "The Atlantic Charter and a Better Bolder League", 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-155, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "Collective Security", 1941 ca. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-156, Author: League of Nations
  - "Draft Report on Social Economic Reconstruction in the Post - War Settlement", 1943 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-157, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "Falsehoods and Facts About the League of Nations Union Policy", 1942 ca. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-158, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "Hitler's New Order", 1941 ca. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-159, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "The League of Nations Union", 1942 ca. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-160, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "The Minorities Problem", 1942 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-161, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "The Moscow Conference the Four Power Declaration", 1944 ca. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Subject: World War II, Previous folder number: C-4-162, Author: League of Nations Union
  - "Peaceful Change", 1942 ca. (Box 11, Folder 12)